Vitaliy Bekshnev

Contact

Address

Uzbekistan, Tashkent

Phone

+998 93-493-20-38

Email

vy.bekshnev@gmail.com

Additional Skills

Technical skills:

• HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript(ES6), Node.js, Express, React, Redux, Typescript, Sass, Git, Linux, Bash

Certifications & Training:

- The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp
- MIPT CS on Python 3 algorithms and data structures
- MERN Stack Full Ecommerce Site - Using React, Redux, Node.js
- Typescript from zero patterns of project management

Professional Summary

Junior React developer with experience in implementing responsive user interface components. Experienced in MERN stack development. Know how translate designs & wireframes into code and write responsive application interface in JS and React workflow. Have 1+ year of experience in React environment. Handle even my smallest projects with git. Prefer Scss over other preprocessors. Have experience writing in Python and Typescript.

Work Experience

05/2021 - 07/2021

HIS International Tours, Vladivostok, Russia

English Japanese Russian translator

- Translations about tours in Russia targeting Japanese audience
- Translating financial information about tours

05/2022 - 06/2022

Nihon No Keisatsu, Vladivostok

English Russian Japanese translator

04/2022 - Now

Self-Employed

Language Tutor (English, Japanese)

• Teach general and speaking courses for beginner and intermediate learners

Education

09/2018 - 06/2022

Far Eastern Federal University, Vladivostok

- Bachelor of Oriental Studies in Japanese History
- Gained extensive training and successfully accomplished all courses on international communication in Japanese, English and Russian languages.
- Learned a lot of business English and Japanese

Languages

English — C1

Russian — Native

Japanese — JLPT N2

References

Github: https://github.com/rosharp